MARYO JOSEPH **SUMENGE**

0432 279 374 | msumenge@hotmail.com | Taringa QLD 4068

o www.maryo.info

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior web designer, developer and software programmer with one-year client and server side programming language experience. Seeking position in a challenging and rewarding tech environment where I can expand upon my existing skills base while contributing to a lively IT team. Additional background includes working in a team based project using a FDD methodology.

EDUCATION

2013 - CURRENT

Bachelor of Interactive Technologies: Web Development

SAE Institute Brisbane, QLD Australia

RELATED SKILLS

UI and UX design

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Adobe Photoshop and Dreamweaver

JQuery and Ajax GitHub

PHP and MySQL WordPress

SASS and LESS Bootstrap

Codelgniter Node.js

(++Browser debugging

Database design Project management

MVC design Marketing

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team-player with good coordinating skills

Possess strong analytical and problem solving skills

Good written and verbal communication skills

Honest, reliable and punctual

Effective at multi-tasking and able to take directions

Flexible, adaptable and keen to take initiatives

WORK HISTORY

JULY 2015 - CURRENT

Web Developer (Freelancer) | Sigma Digital

Designed and developed web based applications as well as modern responsive website. The processes include layout design, database design, CMS design, graphic design, user testing, SEO, version control and framework implementation.

MARCH 2012 - CURRENT Cleaners at Spotless | University of Queensland Cleaning and Building maintenance

AVAILABILITY

Monday : 08.00am – 08.00pm

Tuesday : 08.00am – 08.00pm

Wednesday : 08.00am – 08.00pm

Thursday : 08.00am – 08.00pm

Friday : -

Saturday : 08.00am – 04.00pm

Sunday : 08.00am – 08.00pm

REFERENCES

James Macaulay

BAM (SAEQ), MDM (UoN)
Department Coordinator for Design, Web & Animation
SAE Creative Media Institute, Australia
j.macaulay@sae.edu

Adriana del Monaco

UX Web designer
Former Facilitator at SAE Creative Media Institute
0435350100
adrianadelmonaco@gmail.com

Nick Coleman

Former Supervisor, Spotless Cleaning Company 0420 231 579